[
    {
        "question": "IC chips used in computers are usually made of?",
        "optionA": "Lead",
        "optionB": "Silicon",
        "optionC": "Gold",
        "optionD": "Chromium",
        "answer": "Lead"
    },

    {
        "question": "Find out the odd one",
        "optionA": "Internet",
        "optionB": " Linux",
        "optionC": " Unix",
        "optionD": "Windows",
        "answer": "Internet"
    },

    {
        "question": "From the following sorting algorithms which algorithm needs the minimum number of swaps?",
        "optionA": "Bubble sort",
        "optionB": "Quick sort",
        "optionC": "Merge sort",
        "optionD": "Selection sort",
        "answer": "Selection sort"
    },

    {
        "question": "What kind of errors can be pointed out by the compiler?",
        "optionA": "Syntax error",
        "optionB": "Symantic error",
        "optionC": "Logical error",
        "optionD": "Internal error",
        "answer": "Syntax error"
    },

    {
        "question": "FAQ stands for?",
        "optionA": "Frequently Asked Questions",
        "optionB": "Favourite Asked Questions",
        "optionC": "Favourite and Answered Questions",
        "optionD": "Frequently Answered Questions",
        "answer": "Frequently Asked Questions"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one of the following can not be scheduled by the kernel?",
        "optionA": "kernel level thread",
        "optionB": "user level thread",
        "optionC": "process",
        "optionD": "none of the mentioned",
        "answer": " user level thread"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which algorithm is defined in Time quantum?",
        "optionA": "shortest job scheduling algorithm",
        "optionB": "round robin scheduling algorithm",
        "optionC": "priority scheduling algorithm",
        "optionD": "multilevel queue scheduling algorithm",
        "answer": "round robin scheduling algorithm"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which of the following closely resembles Create view?",
        "optionA": "Create table . . .like",
        "optionB": "Create table . . . as",
        "optionC": "With data",
        "optionD": "Create view as",
        "answer": "Create table . . . as"
    },

    {
        "question": " Aggregate functions are functions that take a ___________ as input and return a single value.?",
        "optionA": "Collection of values",
        "optionB": "Single value",
        "optionC": "Street Racing",
        "optionD": "Both Collection of values & Single value",
        "answer": "Collection of values"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which model in system modelling depicts the dynamic behaviour of the system ?",
        "optionA": "Context Model",
        "optionB": "Behavioral Model",
        "optionC": "Data Model",
        "optionD": "Object Model",
        "answer": "Behavioral Model"
    },

    {
        "question": "The UML supports event-based modeling using ____________ diagrams.?",
        "optionA": "Deployment",
        "optionB": "Collaboration",
        "optionC": "State chart",
        "optionD": "All of the mentioned",
        "answer": " State chart"
    },

    {
        "question": "In a Javascript Application what function can be used to send messages to users requesting for an text input?",
        "optionA": "Display()",
        "optionB": "Alert()",
        "optionC": " GetOutput()",
        "optionD": "Prompt()",
        "answer": "Prompt()"
    },

    {
        "question": "What does error 404 or Not Found error while accessing a URL mean?",
        "optionA": "The server could not find the requested URL",
        "optionB": "Requested HTML file is not available",
        "optionC": "The path to the interpreter of the script is not valid",
        "optionD": "The requested HTML file does not have sufficient permissions",
        "answer": "The server could not find the requested URL"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which of these is a client server application?",
        "optionA": "Web browsing",
        "optionB": "E-mail",
        "optionC": "Internet Chat",
        "optionD": "Thomas Edison",
        "answer": "All of the above"
    },

    {
        "question": "How do I add scrolling text to my page?",
        "optionA": " <scroll>",
        "optionB": "<marquee>",
        "optionC": "<ciruler>",
        "optionD": "<tab>",
        "answer": "<marquee>"
    }
]
